<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SDK on Binary Builders</title><link>https://binary.builders/tags/sdk/</link><description>Recent content in SDK on Binary Builders</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:49:53 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://binary.builders/tags/sdk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unburdened By What Has Been</title><link>https://binary.builders/blog/unburdened-by-what-has-been/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binary.builders/blog/unburdened-by-what-has-been/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>This Blogpost has originally been published on &lt;a href="https://medium.com/the-interchain-foundation/unburdened-by-what-has-been-a90cd3febefb">Medium&lt;/a>&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Interchain Stack is one of the most widely used stacks for building sovereign decentralized applications. We’ve already seen hundreds of chains launch, with many more teams preparing to launch in the coming quarters.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In 2023, the Cosmos SDK team took a step back and asked ourselves, “How can we level up the software to provide more freedom for application developers?” This led us down two development avenues: v2 and CrossLang. This article focuses on v2 — stay tuned for more on CrossLang.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Olympus Rises: A New Era for the Cosmos SDK</title><link>https://binary.builders/blog/olympus-rises-new-era/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binary.builders/blog/olympus-rises-new-era/</guid><description>&lt;p>We are thrilled to announce the latest release of the Cosmos SDK, &lt;strong>Olympus (v0.52)&lt;/strong>. This release marks a significant evolution in the SDK, bringing a host of new features, improvements, and performance enhancements.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-journey-so-far">The Journey So Far&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Cosmos SDK was conceived as a modular framework for building application-specific blockchains, with the vision of enabling seamless connections between chains via IBC. From the early days of development, starting in 2018, the rapidly evolving blockchain space made it challenging to predict its direction. During this period, the team focused on building a robust foundation for the SDK, anticipating current needs and ensuring flexibility to accommodate future trends.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>