<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Events on Binary Builders</title><link>http://localhost:1313/events/</link><description>Recent content in Events on Binary Builders</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Binary Builders Blockchain Summit</title><link>http://localhost:1313/events/blockchain-summit-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/events/blockchain-summit-2025/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Binary Builders Blockchain Summit is our flagship conference bringing together the brightest minds in blockchain technology. Join us for keynote speeches, technical workshops, and networking opportunities with industry leaders and innovators shaping the future of decentralized systems.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Cosmos Ecosystem Hackathon</title><link>http://localhost:1313/events/cosmos-hackathon-2025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/events/cosmos-hackathon-2025/</guid><description>&lt;p>Join the Binary Builders team for an intensive three-day hackathon focused on building the next generation of applications in the Cosmos ecosystem. Learn about the latest SDK features, Rollkit technology, and get hands-on mentorship from our experienced developers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Cosmos SDK Developer Conference</title><link>http://localhost:1313/events/sdk-conference-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/events/sdk-conference-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Cosmos SDK Developer Conference brought together core developers and blockchain engineers to explore the latest advancements in the Cosmos SDK. The event featured technical workshops, protocol discussions, and presentations on upcoming features and improvements to the ecosystem.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Validator Workshop Series</title><link>http://localhost:1313/events/validator-workshop-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/events/validator-workshop-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>Our validator workshop series provided comprehensive training on running professional validator operations. Participants learned about infrastructure setup, security best practices, monitoring solutions, and effective stake management strategies. The recorded sessions are available for reference.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>