<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Updates on Binary Builders</title><link>https://binary.builders/tags/updates/</link><description>Recent content in Updates on Binary Builders</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:37:40 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://binary.builders/tags/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A new fresh look</title><link>https://binary.builders/blog/a-new-fresh-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binary.builders/blog/a-new-fresh-look/</guid><description>&lt;p>We just launched our redesigned website, and wanted to share a quick update about it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We felt it was time to refresh our online presence. Our new site strips away the unnecessary and focuses on what really matters - showing you who we are and what we do in the blockchain space.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We went back to basics with a clean, straightforward approach that makes it easier to find information about our services, team, and projects.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A New Direction</title><link>https://binary.builders/blog/a-new-direction/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binary.builders/blog/a-new-direction/</guid><description>&lt;p>After working in the epicenter of the Cosmos ecosystem for 6 years, I have decided not to continue down the path the ICF is taking. After being at the center of it all for so long I wanted a change of scenery and pace. Cosmos has slowed down and innovation, while still present, is not in the areas I see the future of blockchain going.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I joined for the early vision of Cosmos, one where applications limited in throughput and computation (due to a VM) could build their own chain and define their own constraints. Application developers then began building sovereign chains because there was a premium when raising money for building L1s. This has led to a proliferation of chains launching without market validation. There were countless chains launched with high inflation that ended up robbing the token holders of value since the product was not yet figured out.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>We are Binary Builders</title><link>https://binary.builders/blog/we-are-binary-builders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binary.builders/blog/we-are-binary-builders/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today, we introduce ourselves to the world. At our core, we are builders, that bridge between vision and reality. We push the boundaries of technology with a blend of expertise and enthusiasm. Our mission is to create products that bring the industry forward. As leaders, we are dedicated to excellence, driven by passion and enthusiasm to shape the future of crypto and beyond.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We help teams build, grow, and operate. Executed with love and care.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Unburdened By What Has Been</title><link>https://binary.builders/blog/unburdened-by-what-has-been/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binary.builders/blog/unburdened-by-what-has-been/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>This Blogpost has originally been published on &lt;a href="https://medium.com/the-interchain-foundation/unburdened-by-what-has-been-a90cd3febefb">Medium&lt;/a>&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Interchain Stack is one of the most widely used stacks for building sovereign decentralized applications. We’ve already seen hundreds of chains launch, with many more teams preparing to launch in the coming quarters.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In 2023, the Cosmos SDK team took a step back and asked ourselves, “How can we level up the software to provide more freedom for application developers?” This led us down two development avenues: v2 and CrossLang. This article focuses on v2 — stay tuned for more on CrossLang.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Olympus Rises: A New Era for the Cosmos SDK</title><link>https://binary.builders/blog/olympus-rises-new-era/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binary.builders/blog/olympus-rises-new-era/</guid><description>&lt;p>We are thrilled to announce the latest release of the Cosmos SDK, &lt;strong>Olympus (v0.52)&lt;/strong>. This release marks a significant evolution in the SDK, bringing a host of new features, improvements, and performance enhancements.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-journey-so-far">The Journey So Far&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Cosmos SDK was conceived as a modular framework for building application-specific blockchains, with the vision of enabling seamless connections between chains via IBC. From the early days of development, starting in 2018, the rapidly evolving blockchain space made it challenging to predict its direction. During this period, the team focused on building a robust foundation for the SDK, anticipating current needs and ensuring flexibility to accommodate future trends.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>